<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">[Ðévîçé šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="sim_locked_notification_content">[Åšķ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îƒ ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ бé ûñļöçķéð. Ţåþ ĥéŕé ƒöŕ çöñţåçţ ðéţåîļš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="sim_locked_notification_content_no_contact">[Åšķ ýöûŕ çåŕŕîéŕ îƒ ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ бé ûñļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="sim_locked_notification_title">[ŠÎM çåŕð îšñ’ţ šûþþöŕţéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="sim_unlock_failure_notification_content">[Ýöû’ļļ ñééð ţö çöñţåçţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. Ţåþ ƒöŕ ðéţåîļš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="sim_unlock_failure_notification_content_no_contact">[Ýöû’ļļ ñééð ţö çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ çåŕŕîéŕ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="sim_unlock_failure_notification_title">[Çåŕŕîéŕ ļöçķ çöûļðñ’ţ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="sim_unlocked_notification_content">[Ţĥé ðévîçé çåñ ñöŵ бé ûšéð öñ åñý ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="sim_unlocked_notification_title">[Çåŕŕîéŕ ļöçķ ŕémövéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_disclaimer_no_contact_info">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ĥåš бééñ çöñƒîĝûŕéð ƒöŕ måñåĝéméñţ. Îƒ ţĥîš îš åñ éŕŕöŕ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé’š þŕövîðéŕ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_disclaimer_with_support_link">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ ĥåš šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö бé måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Îƒ ţĥîš îš åñ éŕŕöŕ, &lt;å ĥŕéƒ=ᐅ%2$sᐊ>çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé’š þŕövîðéŕ&lt;/a>.&lt;br>&lt;br>Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ måñåĝé ýöûŕ ðévîçé: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_disclaimer_without_support_link">"[ᐅ%sᐊ ĥåš šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö бé måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Îƒ ţĥîš îš åñ éŕŕöŕ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé’š þŕövîðéŕ.ᐅ
ᐊᐅ
ᐊŢĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ måñåĝé ýöûŕ ðévîçé: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]"</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_header">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé åţ ŵöŕķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_notification_content">[Åûţömåţîçåļļý ŕéšéţţîñĝ šööñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_notification_title">[Ðévîçé måñåĝéð бý åðmîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_reset_disclaimer_with_support_link">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ ĥåš šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö бé måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Îƒ ţĥîš îš åñ éŕŕöŕ, &lt;å ĥŕéƒ=ᐅ%2$sᐊ>çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé’š þŕövîðéŕ&lt;/a>.&lt;br>&lt;br>Ţö çöñţîñûé šéţûþ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ñééðš ţö бé ŕéšéţ. Åļļ ðåţå öñ ţĥé ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé ðéļéţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_reset_disclaimer_without_support_link">"[ᐅ%sᐊ ĥåš šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö бé måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Îƒ ţĥîš îš åñ éŕŕöŕ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé’š þŕövîðéŕ.ᐅ
ᐊᐅ
ᐊŢö çöñţîñûé šéţûþ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ñééðš ţö бé ŕéšéţ. Åļļ ðåţå öñ ţĥé ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé ðéļéţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]"</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_reset_now">[ŕéšéţ ñöŵ one two]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_reset_soon">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ åûţömåţîçåļļý ŕéšéţ šööñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_reset_wait">[öķ one]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_retrieving_header">[Çĥéçķîñĝ ðévîçé îñƒö… one two three]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_retrieving_text">[Ţĥîš ŵöñ’ţ ţåķé ļöñĝ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_support_title">[Šûþþöŕţ one]</string>
    <string name="zero_touch_url_error">[Ţĥîš ļîñķ çåññöţ бé ðîšþļåýéð. one two three four five six seven]</string>
</resources>
